we're going to
write a hash using both the old style
and new style
so i'm going to do this in irb
so let's create an example hash and
first let's write this in the old syntax
style
so i'll wrap my hash and curly braces
and our key will be name and this is a
symbol
we'll use the hash rocket to associate
this key
with the value which is going to be the
string bob
so this hash has one key value pair
a symbol as the key and a string for the
value
so now let's write this same hash in the
newer syntax style and when i press
enter and you see the hash that's
returned from this assignment
you can see that it looks exactly the
same as
the first hash that we wrote on line one
now
this newer syntax only works if your key
is a symbol
if you want your key to be a string or
any other object
then you need to use the older syntax
style with the hash rocket
you